[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "Who is the current Secretary-General of the United Nations as of 2024?",
        "options": [
            "António Guterres",
            "Ban Ki-moon",
            "Kofi Annan",
            "Boutros Boutros-Ghali"
        ],
        "answer": "António Guterres"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Which country hosted the 2023 G20 summit?",
        "options": [
            "India",
            "Italy",
            "Saudi Arabia",
            "Japan"
        ],
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "Which tech company completed the acquisition of Activision Blizzard in 2023?",
        "options": [
            "Apple",
            "Amazon",
            "Microsoft",
            "Google"
        ],
        "answer": "Microsoft"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "What is the name of the recent global initiative to combat climate change launched at COP27?",
        "options": [
            "Green New Deal",
            "Paris Agreement",
            "Glasgow Climate Pact",
            "Climate Action Now"
        ],
        "answer": "Glasgow Climate Pact"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "Who won the 2023 Nobel Prize in Literature?",
        "options": [
            "Abdulrazak Gurnah",
            "Annie Ernaux",
            "Louise Glück",
            "Kazuo Ishiguro"
        ],
        "answer": "Annie Ernaux"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "Which country recently became the newest member of NATO?",
        "options": [
            "Ukraine",
            "Finland",
            "Sweden",
            "Georgia"
        ],
        "answer": "Finland"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "Who is the current Prime Minister of the United Kingdom as of 2024?",
        "options": [
            "Boris Johnson",
            "Rishi Sunak",
            "Liz Truss",
            "Keir Starmer"
        ],
        "answer": "Rishi Sunak"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "Which country won the FIFA Women's World Cup in 2023?",
        "options": [
            "United States",
            "Germany",
            "Brazil",
            "Spain"
        ],
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "What is the name of the mission by NASA that aims to return humans to the Moon by 2025?",
        "options": [
            "Artemis",
            "Apollo",
            "Orion",
            "Discovery"
        ],
        "answer": "Artemis"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "Which country recently legalized same-sex marriage in 2023?",
        "options": [
            "India",
            "Japan",
            "Mexico",
            "Singapore"
        ],
        "answer": "Mexico"
    }
]